http://www.kellogg.northwestern.edu/policies.aspx

COVID-19 Campus Updates
The safety of our community and guests is our first priority.
Learn more about what this means for our phased return to campus
Programs
Why Kellogg
At Kellogg, we develop brave leaders that inspire growth in people, organizations and markets.
Preview Kellogg
What's it like being in a Kellogg MBA program? Find out through this special collection of events, articles, videos and podcasts.
Get to know more about the Kellogg experience
Executive Education
Live Virtual Programs for Fall 2020
Learn from our esteemed faculty in a rich, interactive digital environment, and equip yourself for a new, dynamic business landscape.
Marketing Leaders’ Guide to Analytics and AI
The influence of analytics is only getting stronger: is your organization prepared?
Stay Connected & Be Informed
Create a new profile or update your information in the Northwestern Directory to receive the latest Kellogg news, publications, event invitations and alumni benefit updates.
Visit Our Northwestern today!
Connect
Clubs & Affinity Networks
Reunion Classes by Year
Kellogg Alumni Council
Pete Henderson Society
Learn & Develop
Career Development
Career Coaching
Give
Why Give?
Ways to Give
Kellogg Leadership Circle
Our Donors
Profile
Directory
Contact Us
Donate Now
About
Effective Date: March 28, 2018
The Kellogg School of Management recognizes that visitors to our site may be concerned about the information they provide to us and how we handle that information. This Privacy Notice describes the types of information we collect from and about you when you visit this website (and the mobile optimized version of this website), how we may use and disclose such information, and your ability to control certain uses of it.
Information We Collect
Personally-Identifiable Information
We collect certain personally-identifiable information, such as your name, telephone number and e-mail address, if you choose to register on our website, attend an event or apply to one of our programs. We don’t require you to register or provide personally-identifiable information to view our site or access much of its content but, if you register, you may use certain additional features that allow you to interact with us. Sharing this additional information with us also helps us customize your website experience and interactions.  Here are the ways we collect personally-identifiable information.
Registration
To apply to or interact with Kellogg School, you may choose to register on one or more of our sites. In the registration process, we request certain information (such as your contact information and age) so we can provide you with the communications you request, tailor our website to better meet your needs and customize our contacts with you.
E-mail
When you ask us to send you newsletters, brochures or other content by e-mail, you may provide us with certain information like your e-mail address so we can fulfill your request.
Comments and Other Interactive Features
When you participate in interactive features on our site you may submit information and content, such as comments to the site. You may also provide us with certain information like your e-mail address, city and state of residency. We may use this information to contact you about the content you have provided or to post with your content. Remember that what you post or upload to the site will be publicly available, so please exercise caution when deciding whether to disclose anything personal about yourself. Kellogg School cannot control the actions of third parties who may view the website and use publicly-available information for their own purposes.
Mobile
When you view the site using a mobile device, in addition to the other information we may collect from your actions, we may collect your mobile phone number, device identifier, and geolocation information as well as other non-personal information, such as your device type and carrier.
Send to a Friend
We may give you the opportunity to tell your friends about features or information on our website. If you take advantage of our Send to a Friend option, we ask you for your friend’s and your first name and e-mail addresses to send the information to them that you requested. We don’t keep or use your friend’s e-mail address for any other purpose.
Other Site Features
We offer visitors to our website various features for their enjoyment, which we change from time to time. We may ask you to submit certain personally-identifiable information so we can provide you with these features.
Questionnaires and Surveys
We may ask our website visitors and purchasers to complete surveys and opinion polls to provide feedback on activities, attitudes and interests. These surveys help us understand the needs of our visitors.
Information Collected By Automated Means
We may use cookies, web beacons/pixel tags, log files, and other technologies to collect certain information about visitors to our website, use of our online services, and interactions with our emails and online advertisements. For example, through these means, we may automatically collect information such as your browser type, operating system, mobile device type and carrier, Internet service provider (“ISP”), and IP address. We may also collect information about your use of and interaction with the website (such as the webpages viewed, whether you open, forward, or click-through links, emails, and ads) and other site usage data. Collecting this information, and linking it with your personally-identifiable information, helps us to best tailor our website and enhance your online experience by saving your preferences while you are visiting a particular site, and to help identify site features and content that may be of particular interest to you.
Tracking Options
You can set your Internet browser settings to stop accepting new cookies, to receive notice when you receive a new cookie, to disable existing cookies, and to omit images (which will disable pixel tags). Note that the opt-out will apply only to the browser that you are using when you adjust your tracking settings or cookie preferences. Our system may not respond to Do Not Track requests or headers from some or all browsers. You can learn more about and opt out from receiving third party advertiser cookies by visiting the Digital Advertising Alliance’s opt-out page here. Without cookies or pixel tags though, you may not be able to take full advantage of all of our website features. We adhere to the Digital Advertising Alliance Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising.
Information Collected From Other Sources
We may obtain information about you from other sources, including commercially available sources, such as data aggregators and public databases. This information may include your name, demographic information, interests, and publicly-observed data, such as from social media. We may combine this information with the information we collect from you to help us tailor our communications to you and to improve our services and products.
How We Use Your Information
We may use the information we collect from and about you to contact you from time to time. For example, we may send you communications and information about Kellogg School, our portfolio of programs, our events and our partners. You may receive these offers in advertising that is directed to you via third party sites and media platforms, including in social media. We may respond to your comments or questions, or contact you if needed while processing a product or service you requested through our website. We also may use the information you provide to contact you for your opinions on Kellogg School products, services or websites. As described in this Privacy Notice, we also use the information we collect about you to improve our website, products and services, and to deliver content that is customized to your interests.
How We Share Your Information
We do not sell or otherwise disclose personally identifiable information about our website visitors, except as described here. We do not share your personally identifiable information with unaffiliated third parties for their own marketing purposes without your consent.
We may share personally identifiable information we collect from and about you among Kellogg School programs and initiatives. We may also share the information with service providers we have retained to perform services on our behalf, such as to help run programs and provide customer service. These service providers may have access to personally-identifiable information about our website visitors if it is needed to perform their functions for Kellogg School, but they are not authorized by Kellogg School to use or disclose the information except as necessary to perform services on our behalf or to comply with legal requirements. In addition, we may disclose information where we think it’s necessary to investigate or prevent an actual or suspected crime or injury to ourselves or others, if required by law, or in response to a request from law enforcement authorities or other government officials.
We may share your email address with a third-party, such as a media agency, to send you interest-based advertising on our behalf. We may also share aggregated or de-identified information about you, including based on your email address, with our advertising and marketing partners, and third-party media platforms, including social media sites, to allow them to send targeted advertising messages and/or conduct analyses on our behalf. You may be able to opt out of these ads by clicking on an icon in the ad or through the privacy settings in each social media platform.
We may conduct joint promotions with other companies. We may share with our promotional partners (and their service providers) certain personally-identifiable information as necessary to conduct the promotion. We will not share this information with our promotional partners for any other purpose unless you consent to such sharing.
During the normal course of our business, Kellogg School may sell or purchase assets. If another entity acquires us or any of our assets, information we have collected about you may be transferred to such entity. In addition, if any bankruptcy or reorganization proceeding is brought by or against us, such information may be considered an asset of ours and may be sold or transferred to third parties. Should a sale or transfer occur, we will use reasonable efforts to try to require that the transferee use personally identifiable information provided through this website in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Notice.
Your California Privacy Rights
For California Residents: We may share your personally-identifiable information with affiliated third parties, some of which do not share the Kellogg School name, for their own direct marketing purposes. Because this category of affiliates is considered to be “unaffiliated parties” under California Law, you may opt out of us sharing with them. To opt out, please send a letter with your name, postal address, e-mail, with the heading “California Privacy Rights” to:
Kellogg School
2211 Campus Drive
Evanston, IL 60208
Attention: Creative & Digital Services
Links To Other Websites
This website may contain links to other websites. We provide these links solely for your convenience and information. Different websites have different privacy practices. You should always check the privacy notice of the specific site you’re visiting to understand the privacy practices associated with that site. We are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of third party websites.
Children's Information
This site is intended for general audiences, and Kellogg School does not direct the site to collect, or knowingly collect, any personal information from children under the age of 13.
How We Protect Your Information
The security of personally-identifiable information is important to us. We maintain administrative, technical and physical safeguards to protect against unauthorized use, disclosure, alteration or destruction of the personally-identifiable information we collect on this website. While we make every effort to help ensure the integrity and security of our network and systems, we cannot guarantee our security measures.
Updates To This Privacy Notice
We may change or update portions of this Privacy Notice at any time. Please check back from time to time so you are aware of any changes or updates to the notice. We will indicate the notice’s effective date on the first page of the notice.
Pages in Policy Statements
Policy Statements
Kellogg Honor Code
Kellogg Etiquette
Campus Safety & Clery Act
Kellogg Faculty Policies
Campuses
Chicago
